<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <MAP_Mech_BandwidthLink.label>bandwidth coordination module</MAP_Mech_BandwidthLink.label>
  <MAP_Mech_BandwidthLink.description>A bandwidth coordination module is an information processing device modified from a mechlink, designed for mechanoid use rather than establishing a direct master control link. This module is designed for information distribution and command conversion, enabling the installer to participate in bandwidth transmission as a sub-node, thereby assisting in bearing the mechanitor's control load.\n\nStructurally, the bandwidth coordination module retains the core bionic components of the mechlink used for sensing and parsing psychic signals, but its interfaces and protocols have been comprehensively restructured for mechanoid control units. After installation, the mechanoid will be able to receive high-level commands from the master node and complete necessary signal translation, caching, and redistribution locally, making command flow in the cluster more stable.\n\nSince this module still relies on the dual mechanism of psychic and electromagnetic signals, its operation requires maintaining a minimum level of psychic perception. To ensure the reliability of command parsing and synchronization processes, the module actively calibrates and maintains the installer's psychic sensitivity, preventing it from falling below the level required for coordination due to external factors.\n\nUnlike the mechlink, the bandwidth coordination module does not establish a complete psychic master control relationship, nor does it grant the user direct control over mechanoids. It is more like a relay and stabilization device deployed within the mechanoid system, enabling mechanoids to bear limited command processing and cluster synchronization responsibilities while maintaining a controlled state, thereby maintaining overall coordination in high-load environments.</MAP_Mech_BandwidthLink.description>
  <MAP_Mech_BandwidthLink.descriptionShort>A coordination module modified from a mechlink, enabling mechanoids to participate in command transmission and processing as bandwidth sub-nodes.</MAP_Mech_BandwidthLink.descriptionShort>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_EfficientExecution.label>behavior mode: efficient execution</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_EfficientExecution.label>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_EfficientExecution.description>Under Justice's coordination, this mechanoid adopts an efficient work behavior mode optimized by the superior coordination unit, efficiently reorganizing task order and paths. Without changing basic performance, overall work efficiency is improved and energy consumption is reduced.</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_EfficientExecution.description>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_EfficientExecution.descriptionShort>Under Justice's coordination, this mechanoid is in an efficient execution state</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_EfficientExecution.descriptionShort>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_MobileCombat.label>behavior mode: mobile combat</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_MobileCombat.label>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_MobileCombat.description>Under Justice's coordination, this mechanoid adopts a mobile combat behavior mode optimized by the superior coordination unit. The integrated gait control system makes its movement unaffected by terrain, while the fire control calculation module simultaneously compresses post-firing recovery intervals and can somewhat avoid incoming damage. Mechanoids in this mode ignore terrain penalties when moving.</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_MobileCombat.description>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_MobileCombat.descriptionShort>Under Justice's coordination, this mechanoid is in a mobile combat state</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_MobileCombat.descriptionShort>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_FortifiedDefense.label>behavior mode: fortified defense</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_FortifiedDefense.label>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_FortifiedDefense.description>Under Justice's coordination, this mechanoid adopts a fortified defense behavior mode optimized by the superior coordination unit, using a position anchoring system to actively limit mobility in exchange for shorter aiming and firing recovery intervals, and significantly improved shooting stability.</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_FortifiedDefense.description>
  <MAP_Justice_WorkMode_FortifiedDefense.descriptionShort>Under Justice's coordination, this mechanoid is in a fortified defense state</MAP_Justice_WorkMode_FortifiedDefense.descriptionShort>
</LanguageData>
