<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <MAP_Mech_Justice.label>Justice</MAP_Mech_Justice.label>
  <MAP_Mech_Justice.description>A mechanoid commander designed for mechanoid cluster command. Justice does not excel in direct combat, but exists as an extended mechanitor node, continuously sharing communication bandwidth with mechanitors and expanding command range. Through a built-in specially tuned bandwidth coordination module, it can support caravan command and high-load multi-tasking, enabling mechanoids to maintain stable execution efficiency during extended operations.\n\nUnlike most mechanoids, Justice's combat and execution protocols are not fixed. It can quickly switch operating modes based on battlefield and mission environments, and synchronize its state corrections and command logic to controlled mechanoids, thereby improving overall coordination and mobility without significantly increasing individual burden.\n\nDespite its primary responsibility for coordination and command, Justice retains basic combat capabilities, can freely use human weapons, and has quite reliable social and crafting logic. This makes it not only a command center during wartime in the mechanoid system, but also capable of taking on coordination and maintenance roles during non-combat phases. Some colony records indicate that as long as Justice is still running, mechanoid cluster actions appear exceptionally restrained and efficient, as if the entire system is constantly being calibrated.</MAP_Mech_Justice.description>
  <MAP_Mech_Hermit.label>Hermit</MAP_Mech_Hermit.label>
  <MAP_Mech_Hermit.description>Hermit is a mechanoid equipped with high-power signal relay devices, carrying a bandwidth information processing module with independent bandwidth. This mechanoid can precisely receive command signals from mechanitors, operate outside mechanitor range, and independently lead caravans.\n\nNote: Mechanoids controlled by Hermit can only be drafted within its control range.</MAP_Mech_Hermit.description>
  <MAP_MechBandwidthLink.label>bandwidth coordination module</MAP_MechBandwidthLink.label>
  <MAP_MechBandwidthLink.description>A bandwidth coordination module is an information processing device modified from a mechlink, designed for mechanoid use rather than establishing a direct master control link. This module is designed for information distribution and command conversion, enabling the installer to participate in bandwidth transmission as a sub-node, thereby assisting in bearing the mechanitor's control load.\n\nStructurally, the bandwidth coordination module retains the core bionic components of the mechlink used for sensing and parsing psychic signals, but its interfaces and protocols have been comprehensively restructured for mechanoid control units. After installation, the mechanoid will be able to receive high-level commands from the master node and complete necessary signal translation, caching, and redistribution locally, making command flow in the cluster more stable.\n\nSince this module still relies on the dual mechanism of psychic and electromagnetic signals, its operation requires maintaining a minimum level of psychic perception. To ensure the reliability of command parsing and synchronization processes, the module actively calibrates and maintains the installer's psychic sensitivity, preventing it from falling below the level required for coordination due to external factors.\n\nUnlike the mechlink, the bandwidth coordination module does not establish a complete psychic master control relationship, nor does it grant the user direct control over mechanoids. It is more like a relay and stabilization device deployed within the mechanoid system, enabling mechanoids to bear limited command processing and cluster synchronization responsibilities while maintaining a controlled state, thereby maintaining overall coordination in high-load environments.\n\n Select the target mechanoid and right-click this device to issue an installation command.</MAP_MechBandwidthLink.description>
</LanguageData>
