<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <MechCommander.Messages.Justice.CannotBeControlledByMech>Justice cannot be controlled by other mechanoids</MechCommander.Messages.Justice.CannotBeControlledByMech>
  <MechCommander.Messages.Hermit.CannotBeControlledByMech>Hermit cannot be controlled by other mechanoids</MechCommander.Messages.Hermit.CannotBeControlledByMech>
  <MechCommander.Messages.BandwidthLink.CannotBeControlledByMech>Mechanoids with bandwidth coordination module installed cannot be controlled by other mechanoids</MechCommander.Messages.BandwidthLink.CannotBeControlledByMech>
  <MechCommander.Bill.Reason.JusticeCannotGestate>Justice cannot be gestated by mechanoids</MechCommander.Bill.Reason.JusticeCannotGestate>
  <MechCommander.Letter.BandwidthLinkInstalled.Label>Bandwidth coordination module installed</MechCommander.Letter.BandwidthLinkInstalled.Label>
  <MechCommander.Letter.BandwidthLinkInstalled.Body>{PAWN} has installed a bandwidth coordination module! This mechanoid can now share bandwidth and relay commands, acting as a sub-node in mechanoid cluster coordination and control.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About controlling mechanoids:(/SectionTitle)After installing the bandwidth coordination module, the installer can control other mechanoids like a mechanitor by right-clicking. Mechanoids with the bandwidth coordination module installed will exist as independent coordination nodes and cannot be controlled by other mechanoids.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About control range:(/SectionTitle)Thanks to the modifiability of mechanoids, the bandwidth coordination module is no longer limited by implant volume and can carry larger-scale information processing and transmission components. Therefore, the installer is no longer limited by distance when controlling other mechanoids, and can operate independently outside the mechanitor's control range.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About caravans:(/SectionTitle)Through localization of command parsing and execution processes, mechanoids with the module installed can precisely execute high-level commands from mechanitors. This enables them to independently lead caravans without requiring human colonists.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About psychic sensitivity:(/SectionTitle)The link between mechanitors and mechanoids relies not only on electromagnetic signals but also on psychic communication. The bandwidth coordination module has restructured the psychic link components of the mechlink, enabling it to actively calibrate and maintain psychic perception, ensuring the installer's psychic sensitivity never falls below 100% to ensure command stability.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About bandwidth:(/SectionTitle)Like the mechlink, the bandwidth coordination module provides 6 bandwidth capacity in its initial state. However, unlike human mechanitors, mechanoids can further expand bandwidth by installing high-tier mechanoid chips. Select the installer and right-click the corresponding chip to command installation. Synchronization signal chips provide 5 bandwidth, power convergence chips provide 10 bandwidth, and nanostructuring chips provide 15 bandwidth. A mechanoid with the bandwidth coordination module installed supports up to 100 bandwidth.</MechCommander.Letter.BandwidthLinkInstalled.Body>
  <MechCommander.Letter.JusticeGestated.Label>About Justice</MechCommander.Letter.JusticeGestated.Label>
  <MechCommander.Letter.JusticeGestated.Body>You have successfully gestated a Justice. Justice is a mechanoid commander designed for mechanoid cluster command, with a built-in persona core that gives it highly human-like behavior and decision-making capabilities. Compared to ordinary mechanoids that only have the bandwidth coordination module installed, Justice performs more efficiently in command and coordination, with comprehensive capabilities that can even surpass ordinary human mechanitors.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About bandwidth coordination module:(/SectionTitle)Justice fully inherits all functions of the bandwidth coordination module, with specialized adaptations for some mechanisms. It has a 150 bandwidth cap and 5 control groups, and can continue commanding mechanoids even when unable to act. Justice will attempt to synchronize beneficial states it receives to its controlled mechanoids. These mechanoids can also use special work modes that provide benefits.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About mechanitor tasks:(/SectionTitle)Thanks to advanced operation and processing modules, Justice can handle most tasks that originally required human mechanitors, including gestating mechanoids, summoning mechanoid bosses, and repairing damaged mechanoids. Additionally, Justice can perform ordinary manual work.\n\n(*SectionTitle)About persona simulation system:(/SectionTitle)The persona core carried by Justice enables it to simulate human behavior to the greatest extent, allowing players to direct it to prioritize specific work like a colonist. Justice can use human weapons, assign work priorities through the work panel, trade with caravans, or lead caravans to faction settlements for trade. It can also independently pilot shuttles and use communication consoles for contact. When its mechanoid skill level is higher than the panel skill level, Justice will attempt to synchronize the skill level to the panel level.</MechCommander.Letter.JusticeGestated.Body>
</LanguageData>
